Uh-huh. Right. You're starting in four. Oh, yeah. Thank you next thing because the countdown. What's up? Yeah, that was interesting. I mean
What happened? I mean
Yes, there's just certain things I
Was already going to leave it but I was I was just like waiting for something so I'm really ridiculous and then she said that
Really terrible thing where you should never like say you're gonna do that
I would not like to happen on my stream and say, you know, maybe, you know, if you're thinking about that kind of thing, you know
You can get some help
Because it seems like a serious problem
Yeah, yeah, we need to buy but I definitely need to do that. That was just like, you know, it's like
you know
I've had people say oh I own the show I own the show like a lot of people have said that and then a lot of people
A lot of people have been accused of that too, but I've never tried to like you know take over the show. It's like
You know, it's like saying it's like someone like claiming it's like, you know, this is my baby
It's not like you know, that's just for people to pass around like a football, you know, it's like
So I'm I'm I get a protective kind of feeling toward it
It makes me a little crazy sometimes, but
But it'll be okay, it'll be okay
Hi Jamie
Thank You Cristina
Yeah, it's it's been difficult and I think especially you know in this community all these all these like you know
Like I said, West Side story so all these rival factions coming together and and then there's people that with from with
Different factions that fall in love and stuff and then everyone goes up. You know goes crazy. I
Try to say out of it, but
Yeah, and yeah, well, you know, I was willing to let them have their
have their say, you know
It seemed like it seemed like a nice couple, you know, I don't know until first impressions
They were you know, he seemed a little he seemed a little upset
I but I don't know I'm sure they're making more history than I'm aware of there's always two sides of the story
I'm not really here. The show's not really about getting involved in that and
so I think we should like kind of like start to
cool it a little bit on the
some of these like
Drama panels, especially when it gets into such a sticky territory like doxing and slander and stuff like that
Which is like against my rules and just not for my show. And so, you know
I'm happy to have you know, I'm gonna participate in chat, but I'm gonna have to be like, you know
Little bit. I want a different formula for
My panels
Any panel for you?
I hate blackout, Andy, how are you?
Yeah, but it's like, you know, it's like, and it's like,
and I'm going to have to go through like, you know,
mods again and things like that.
I just, you know, I've seen a couple of mods.
I really don't need many.
It's like, there's people that are,
I have some super mods that are like,
they're here almost at the beginning of every show.
They're just like, they're so awesome.
And it's like, and those are like the, you know,
It's a good balance is like I think there's only some of the only good ones
you know that so much and then I like the people that are like also not
really doing you know interfering too much in the chat or just looking out for the interests of the show
But you know, but who's really to be trusted there's like there's a good saying trust no one okay trust no one
you know, you should always
You never you never know someone 100 right?
I
You guys have bodies in your
It buried your backyard. I would have no idea, right? So who knows but
like
If I judge, you know
This might be a little bit more hesitant on me a person. Yeah, it's so busy doing
Yeah, you're busy. Yeah, it's a busy during the summer family of the summer. Yeah. Hey Alex
Yeah, it's just no one but it's like, you know, it's like the other at the end of the day like 30 diamonds at the end of the day
The end of the day. It's my show
Whatever happens to my show happens to me, you know, doesn't have any video except, you know
I do feel like people would lose out on a good show. It's like, you know
You know where they can like, you know, pretty much everyone's welcome to come. There's a lot of diversity. It's like a kind of different
There's different stuff going on here. It's just like I think it's a good I'm a fan of my own show
I would watch my show
That's how you know, it's like good. I watch it sometimes. I'm a little shocked at what I say and
It's the kind of watching a different person sometimes, but
That happens sometimes they get this up
Personality takes over
How's life treating me pretty pretty good? I'm enjoying my
When you light and my car lemonade
Yeah, I think we have we have really great people here
I think you know even even like the trolls are like I look for I was like, oh
You know look forward to some of them sometimes just but I'm not the not the really bad souls, but
Because those people that say really mean thing like really just like I know just to hurt my feelings
There's like six days of work. I know it's just trolling, but it's like there's just some meet really mean things that I don't care
But it's like I can laugh at like
certain thing but it's like
Some things we got way too
cruel, I don't know
But that's not only people who would boost the hive if it was too cruel
Yeah, and that's kind of like my inner protector taking over nice hard the minute is a Canadian. It's Canadian. Yeah
Yeah, let's always raise the vibes. Let's like have a
like I think we can like
Do a few of these who-do cards? I'll read and this who Jack I have and then they just will maybe like, you know
Maybe like put things in a different
Vibration, I mean sometimes it's like you experiment with James, and I don't know what's gonna happen, but that's part of the fun
experimenting
Unless there's a big explosion it can interesting things can happen. Okay, so let's see
There's a few cards
Hi guys
We're here me, okay, okay
Okay
All right, are you looking at tricks?
Yeah, it's your tricks back there.
Hey, Tristie.
There's Rudy right here.
Hey, Rudy.
The cats are all sitting around.
So you got Lola here too.
Lola, do you want to say hi to the camera?
Oh, I still got the full screen.
And it's Lola.
Your little grumpy face.
You have a grumpy face?
Are you making a face that...
Some of the mean people in chat. Oh, okay go over there
Yeah, she's like, I don't want to get involved in your personal shit. I know I see her
Okay
How's that yeah daughter of truth, okay, thank you and see
Hi, baby
They can't throw your breeze right there. Hey
You're a good good day, you have a good day tricks like that you're having a good day watching the house
Okay, so let's do three cards. Okay
Okay, thank you, you know, thank you easy
for
providing this
sponsoring this deck for the chat
This is a really awesome deck.
Okay, we got this Mother of Sticks.
We got the Mother of Sticks.
And so, I guess I believe the sticks are the wands
and she's having a cigarette there.
So I'm looking at a little cigarette.
I think she has a little bird right there,
a little bird sitting there too.
Little, I think that little bird tells her things.
I think he's lighting her cigarette there,
but yeah, that little bird tells her things, okay.
So the Mother of Sticks, okay.
So it says mother of six. It says her plant is tobacco. And so maybe if I smoke some more tobacco
I can get into her energy. She's smoking right there
Who do is like a lot about these details and like actually practice, you know, incorporate some of these things and as you know for
different spiritual reasons, the mother of six is shown with a crown of tobacco leaves that is reminiscent of early
Colonialized era black virginian advertisements. She's wearing a tartan fastened with a goose a
Grouse foot brooch as a good luck charm
The mother of six pipe is lit by a kite of the kite of the bird, right?
There are five kites living in the southern United States and like the mother of six those beautiful
Raptors are determined to keep moving forward so much that they never take a break, they eat, drink, and even bathe and flight.
Well, how about that? That sounds a little bit like me sometimes, but can we all relate to that though?
You know the determination a lot of this show like you know, and I know because things will happen
It's panel reading others for everybody. Yeah, I'll put a link after the after the panel reading. That's gonna decide
There's a couple more cards
but it says
The mother of six is one of the most uplifting cards of the deck on the positive side
She is optimistic fiery
Confident courageous focused and powerful on the negative side
She is also malicious overbearing arrogant two-faced a workaholic or a major drama queen
Interreading if she doesn't represent a literal person with these qualities that she represents these attributes
Okay, so
You know and then you know, they also I love how they have the and I like to read the positive and negative with you know
With these cars, you know, sometimes we just have one interpretation
But you know, these are kind of balanced in that
Yeah, there's a negative side this be recognized to there's not just all good cars are not all bad cars
There's there's a there's negative attributes. It could be pointing out and it's like we should really consider
You know if we carry these attributes and you know work on them, too, right?
Because we can always improve that's what it's really about. It's like self-improvement, right?
Because we are we can we are own own temple or own work of art, right?
Or a house for the higher spirit, okay, so now we have the ace of coins, okay?
Wow, so there's like you see the hand and there's that there's a piece of pie right there, okay?
I remember this card. I think we got this the first day, but you'll love this card, okay?
So yeah, they make a pie, they put different things in the pie, and so they put one of
the things is the coin, and you can see the coin right there.
It's kind of like, you got a piece of pie with lucky coin in it, right?
Okay.
You know, ace of coins, the ace of pentacles, it's a seed, it's like something from God
too, I believe, you know, from the divine, handing it to you to nurture and grow, right?
Okay, so we have the Ace of Coins.
Okay.
Ace of Coins says...
A woman holds a slice of sweet potato pie
on a serving knife to offer her guests. The pie was baked
with a lucky Indian head penny.
a shiny piece of ragged cloth, a matchstick, a pea, and a ring inside.
Inspired by the traditional Irish born broccoli bread, the coin symbolizes wealth, the cloth symbolizes poverty,
the pea symbolizes not getting married, the matchstick symbolizes domestic discord, and the ring symbolizes getting married.
Receiving a slice with lucky penny, but she also has received a message in the tea leaves for telling good fortune ahead fortune ahead
Oh, my mic is crackly. Oh
Thanks money for 20
My mic is crackly. I'm sorry. I bought a nail. I've been a clipper. My nails got really dirty. I'm sorry
But it says meaning positive inheritance receiving money or gifts new financial or career opportunities
productivity fertility job offers abundance
practical advice
Achieving tangible results blessings lottery winnings optimism
money reward for hard work
Inspired and improved health happy new beginnings
Having a support system
Manifestation windfalls and good omens, and I will just leave this and thank you for the super chat money for 20
I will leave this part of the upright though
Yeah, I will live down the upright and not really in until it's reversed
I'll read the negative meaning but let's just have the optimism that it is all these good things and there's you know
Because we all know the the other the other side of that coin, right?
We know the the bad things, but we went we went all positive things, right?
So let's just take that as the positive omen that
We have good things happening by an opportunity. Okay, so then we have okay
Here's the last one. We have the grandchildren. This is called the grandchildren. Okay. It's a grandchildren. I
believe you know
Hooters tradition is about a lot about the ancestors and so I would say, you know
This is basically from the ancestors. Okay, it says it's the ancestors of the grandchildren. Okay, so
She's the grandchildren. It's number
I've never seen it so it's number 17. Oh, that's the tower cars. Okay. Oh, wow
But again, I saw
Some good interpretations of the tower card there are there are some good interpretations
But let's see number 17 the tower. I think it's the tower isn't
No, it's not something terrible. I'm sorry. The grandchildren is the star. Oh, yeah, 17 is the star. I'm sorry the star card
Well, that means make a wish, right?
means make a wish. I think I was on the tower, I was getting scared for a second.
Okay, there's a star, and there's a little star flower in there too. Okay,
enhance. Okay, it says, and there's a Genesis, there's a the Genesis quote, it
says, early the next morning, Leibon kissed his grandchildren and his daughters
and blessed them. Then he left and returned home.
So it says Genesis 31, 55.
So that's not about, you know, like our grandparents,
the kids that they're growing, you know,
and then it's said, you know, they're still with us,
you know, and that's all our ancestors.
A grandparent cubs the child's tiny hands
as the child holds a star-shaped flower.
It says, since time immemorial, humans have been fascinated by the stars, not only because
they're beautiful, but also because they represent our highest goals, dreams, and aspirations.
In black American families, the star should be analogous to one's grandchildren as the
ultimate symbol of hope.
After centuries of terrorism, psychological warfare, enslavement, and oppressive legislation,
Their progeny will not only survive, but will also finally be allowed to thrive.
They hope that they will not have to beg or ask permission to exist, and will finally
be able to live their lives on their own terms.
It is on the grandchildren that wishes were earnestly placed.
And it says, meaning, when the grandchildren appears and are reading as a sign that relief
Is there no sign of hope evident in your life yet?
If there is no sign of hope evident in your life yet, just be patient and you will soon see the proof that things are looking up.
Blessings shall abound. If you receive the grandchildren in a reading, consider the following.
So ask yourself these questions or consider these things. Do I regularly count my blessings?
Believing doesn't require proof. What can I do to regain hope?
Find a way to become inspired.
Give without seeking any return, anything in return.
What motivates you to get up in the morning
and do it again?
Miracles happen every day.
Why can't they happen to you?
Perhaps it's time for the old and young
to get together and enjoy to this company.
Blessings are on the way.
It might be time to share some of the words of wisdom
with some younger or less mature.
It says all will turn out right in the end.
And that's a beautiful message for the reading.
I really love that.
And it's like, I hope you liked that too,
and I hope it resonated with you.
But it really did hit home with me,
and that just made a lot of sense.
And that was for everybody,
but take what with it would resonate.
It's really interesting.
I think we should all be allowed to thrive here,
and I know we've had like a history of humanity of,
You know, you know, some some groups over taking their other groups and stuff like that
But I think we've worked together coexist. It would be even
Be even better everyone could be happy, you know
Thank you money for that super chat, okay, I'll put the link up. Yeah
So let's have a, let's have a, let's have a like a, you know, a peaceful, like I want to have a peaceful kind of night.
So let's not come up here on the piano. I know, I know everyone knows already, but let's not come up to like fire or, or we had, we had the drama portion of the show.
And now it's like, you know, kind of speaking, just relax and have fun and not worry about that.
You know until it finally like it seems like so big it's like and I have to reach out to address it and kind of like
slay the dragon a little bit, but
You know, I'm sure there'll be other dragons. Oh
Shit, I really really came over my help explain here
Hey, where do you want to say hi to the chat?
Do you want to say hi you came over to say hi
We want to be here. Hey, we have Dougie Doug here
Hi
Hey, what's up psych? How are you? I'm doing good. I'm gonna smoke this bowl and then I'll probably be having a bed
Okay, it's almost two in the month 130 in the morning
Yeah, how's your night?
Yeah, I had I like talking to you there either day, you know, you're but yeah, oh yeah, I talked to a couple times actually and
Always a joy talking to you. So have you seen any of the show tonight? It's been a little bit hectic today
Yeah, I saw that when I came in it was kind of hectic
You said well you said your shows not your shows not like that, right? You know, you you like you don't allow
I don't then anybody but I time people out. I don't think twice about it. They want to come in and talk shit
I just time them out
On the panel though, you said on the panel you don't let them on or if people come on the panel and start getting like that
I do them
But once again, like I said, I don't ban them from my chat room, but I do
Time people out for like 24 hours
Because they could go and you know come back another time, right?
Yeah
I'm not judgmental about how people run their panels every person who has a panel has a right to run it the way they want to and
They should because they should run it the way they want it
They shouldn't do things just because other people do it
They should do things because they think it's the right thing to do right now
Everyone has a different idea about what's the right thing to do and and and and that's fine. Everybody should we are all different
Right. Mm-hmm. So
Just because I you know, don't let that shit go on. It doesn't mean that I don't think I
Mean this place is for that. You know what I mean? There's a time and a place and whatnot
Yeah, and I'm not in any way judgmental about other people how they run their panels. Yeah, boy
I mean, I've like, you know, I've just been I've experienced it with the panel
I basically you know, I've been doing it just for a few months like I think since January I was doing the streamer panels
And it's been quite a learning experience
But it's also I want to like, you know, I like to
Like I just don't like if you're back sit. Yeah, you know, some people get mad if I
Someone just left from backstage. They didn't laugh because I wanted to talk to you for a second. I want to like, you know have like
So you have to say that maybe add them then it's like we run a show and everything and people are always
It's so insulted when they're just not all just not right right when they come and like and they kept there the whole time and like
To do the center of the universe and deserve special treatment everybody
They all everybody thinks that
Yeah, and once again, I know you're monetized. I'm not so I've got nothing. I'm not trying to please anybody
Mm-hmm. I don't give a fuck if people come or not come
You know what I mean? It's like I don't give a shit
Yeah, I'm not I'm not making it cost me money. Yeah
I pay for seeing yards. Exactly. Exactly. I pay for streamers, too
And it's you know, and it's not it's not a cheap. It's not a cheap service. It's an expensive service
And it's like, you know, I know
But it just makes doing the panels easy and I love doing panels and I want to continue doing panels, but it's like they've just been
Like there's been so much negative shit happening just like really recently and it's like even from people that our friends and all of a sudden
They're saying things that I think
Rain is a dumb bitch because okay. Okay. I help here. It's an old folks home all of a sudden
I'm young. I'm young. I don't know what they're talking about
Everybody up here, but it raised rain is in the chat like congratulations. I keep just turning this into a old folks home of some
And so, I mean, it's like, you know, I do have like a demographics of every, you know, every Asian. So, you know, I think the demographic people of the 20s are the same as people in their 60s, probably. So, you know, I, you know,
Of course, you get chat rooms with people from their early 20s to their late 70s and 80s, even all in the same chat room talking.
That's a really cool. That's a really cool thing
And I mean if all the people don't even recognize that I verse it is in the chat because you know is it we just see the text and
Did I read it as a photo? But if we were to see everybody that's in the chat
We'd be like oh my god, it's like it's gonna be like all different races all different
Sex or is it gonna be so it's gonna be so any different interesting people as they
In a real-life scenario you probably would not get such an eclectic group of people together correct correct 100%
100% that would never happen. Exactly. That's why there's a special a little bit in that way doggy dog is smart man
No, we got Sean P is 22
The other day you psyched and he was giving you fucking golden knowledge. Yeah, you know
But he's still been around, you know, he knows what he's talking about
Yeah, and I haven't had so many people give me great advice like him and you know at least they gave me some great advice
He doesn't give me great advice and
I know so I've had some people give me good advice that I recognize when people are trying to like leave me down the wrong path
They're gonna be bad advice or just like so it's like so I I'm like pretty secure and like what I've been told
DJ lecture first, you know, and so it's like I think you're wrong because at first you like everyone's advice
But now you're more like refined
Yeah, honing in on who's advice taken
That's what it is. Some people, you see a person in the relation.
Everybody's advice, but yeah, but make your own decisions as far as you do
The trolls could give him advice I could give him advice Alex to give him advice
But it's up to psyche to choose where you are and I say advice. I don't mean people are like
No, they say hey, you know
Here's how to like handle doing panels and here's how to handle porn bar me use how to handle, you know
like people are going crazy,
doxxing in chat and just get advice like that
to keep it like, you know.
And there are also would just be like
You have to be able to filter and keep the good stuff and you know, like oh take a strainer basically
Oh, this is how you protect your panel. Don't pump on like this do this do that
Yeah, oh, yeah, I'm gonna say and I think it was sold to me in a nice nice way like
I like went to elisa and like people like asking for advice and like, you know, I asked her like elisa about
I was like, what if, you know, I said, you know, I might kind of be, my channel's being attacked and like,
and I'm on a side that she's like, she's like, don't even worry about being monetized. She's like,
because she's like, I mean, she's monetized. She doesn't ask for super chats. She actually says,
don't send a super chat. She doesn't have memberships or anything. I don't even think she plays ads.
She just has her TTS thing going.
She has any completed messages on screen
and she just wants people to donate through that.
And so she's going to use the monetization feature.
And so there's other ways to monetize
and still use YouTube and stuff.
And so, but it's just like, you know.
But you know, I think I've just been under attack by like a lot of different people
But that's kind of the thing I like brought in a lot of different people to the channel
I went to a lot of different panels and like the terrarium for everybody on the panel and then
This is all these different groups came and started in some IPQ channels
You've done very well as far as bringing all different kind of people to your place
That's one thing you've done very well, and I've only been watching you for a few weeks
You know
Yeah
That's how I found your ass from panel happened. I told you I remember he was panel happened to some of us that deals the TPP
And then he got the deals. I found them
Because he's love and love magnetizes people you understand
He just magnetizes every community
The fucking elder the B community the a1 we just want magnetized to this guy
Because of the way he is and it's hard and then there's the people that want to take him down
But I might hear is that now that they've been here for a while. They don't want to take him down anymore
Because they're falling in love with him like everybody
Like
Thank you, and I do love people and I really do like I really like it's like that's why I even like, you know
You know stings those just so much like shit and that's like I still like you know like like him
And then I think I didn't like what he was saying at that or if that was like a stunt to like harm the show or something
Because it's this gives like there's very odd things and then his friend was like oh tell him what tell me his friend his friend 300 glow is like
it's ridiculous it makes them even look more stupid like bro don't you have big
fish to fry i don't know i i never did anything to either i never did either i only had all
i do it's normal piano i just ream on a piano and i was just been constant and that's like the
same i never did anything i was i try to be
Let everybody on it that I can like there's some people that I can't like you know
Like the emcee nemesis came under a different name and I couldn't let them on and yes, and we're bombs
Alex
Wait, do you know who I think that is? I think it's Chris. It's MC. Nemesis ever
They think it's me, I think
MC
hell no
he could never pull that off
it's fucking Chris Cab
Yeah, well, there's no there's somebody that came on the panel their name is well
MC Nemesis was one of the first people to come on my panels and then he does
He's like a kind of disorder where he can't like he gets angry and then he has to say the n-word
And he did it like so many times that I like finally banned him, but he was interesting
No, would you bought someone MC Nemesis or nobody even near like
He was on last night for for hours and like we
Yeah, so I don't know people think it's me
As you do you think everyone's everywhere and then it's like when finally we find something that is that you don't believe
That's why I call you the fucking expect easy. That's what I call you to expect
Well, that's a whole different ballgame there. Let me expect I add to my inspection
This happened years ago. I mean we confronted matter of fact. It was me
Dubbs you could go to Dubb's page. You got it there. It's me Dubbs and OG bottle
or
My boy by the way, but it's not coming you but we work cut from the same cloth
You know, well, I thought it was you probably
Recognize some of like your cadence in the voice and then I can't say is that I was like no no no
My beard was long and then he came on he came on he came he came up
He had a red hat on and a blue hoodie. I said look at this nigga looking like Papa Smurf
And I look like this nigga with the big head. I'm chopping my jump off
The bubbles getting that og bottle and then it was argue it. Yeah. He's like, yeah
Yeah, I'm this guy. I'm that guy and then he said the n-word over and over and over
Yeah, yeah, you are closer. Oh a really good person by the way. It's like that's not like a bad dad
It's like oh someone you want on your side
No, but he put the chairs
That's that's what a MCM assist those two. Hey, I was gonna let you on
I just wouldn't want to talk to Dougie for like on like 101 for just a few minutes and then I was gonna let you on
You can come now. It's like I wasn't I didn't like ban you or anything from the pain
Yeah, yeah, but I mean as long as you know you behave yourself
Yeah, it's like I have to admit and then JC like
No, I mean, it's crystal, and they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they're really, they
You guys, I don't want to ban from the panel.
The money, feedback, you know.
You bring them up, bro.
No, I don't.
Yeah, the people, if people start changing around,
they're photographs to different,
other people, I just have to ban you from the panel
because I just don't do that at all, okay?
One photo rule.
There's a one photo rule.
Use your own photo.
I heard and I even responded to in the chat.
Don't take sides in people's personal shit.
I'm not taking sides
It's very good, but you said about oh yeah, I'm encouraging you
Just like that. I should be like, yo, okay
I don't take sides come up here support both. Let me say this if people don't like that and they tell you oh you have to take
Aside or didn't tell them to go fuck themselves. I don't give a shit
You know, I don't take sides in personal people's personal shit. I'm not for one and against another
I'm trying to support everybody, I'm trying to be friendly with everybody, I don't give a shit if people don't like it, I don't care.
You have to be willing. What I found as a female myself in the panel is that some people are going to get mad and never come back.
Okay, so be that.
I mean, yeah, something will come up on the panel,
and once they get a pair, I'll just leave,
because I just don't want to.
And we can't, we can't cancel other people.
If we just do us and do the best we can,
and then when Ryder, our decision is,
it's like, if they don't like it, you know,
it's like, then they're not in our vibration,
and probably shouldn't be there anyway.
And so it's like, we'll attract people by being authentic,
and then we'll attract people for the right reasons
instead of people falling in love with a fake person,
or, you know,
No, is there a right reason to attack someone in YouTube? It's it's so benign. It's such a
YouTube is such it's like it's all
You know it's all fake. I think I said the last time I was ever I think people in YouTube. They're like actors
Yeah, it's a character
character in YouTube
Yeah, you can you need an avatar play as many characters as you want you can go on different panels and different voice boxes and different avatars and
Some of you can hate somebody on one avatar and they'd be the best friend another and then it's like and then no one will know
Never even knows it's kind of funny, you know, but
I showed you on my habit
Special oh that's special
That's why I don't trust nobody up here you understand you can just shit up here. You don't know who's
No
Panels you can go to where there is none of that bullshit, right? You can always fuck
There's there's hundreds of thousands of YouTube places and people like to be in Alaska in a radio tower right now
Yeah
There's people there's people that just like to like wash lives and they're together different kind of like kind of more social
Even if they're not social in real life and they're social on YouTube and there's like there's a lot of people that are introverts
I come out of their shell on the YouTube chats and like, you know
Because you can say kind of anonymous like that and I think and then they like the interaction like that you can do
You know, it's like a kind of a pretty much a
safe interaction, you're not gonna like,
cause what's talking over the, over the computer,
you're not gonna like, you know,
have any physical, any physical happen,
and it's like, but that's when,
when vaccine stuff starts happening,
push the batteries.
Yeah, go ahead.
Let me respond to Dot.
Yeah, Dot, they've contacted my wife.
Absolutely.
I'm not worried.
You know, if you don't do anything,
if you have nothing to worry about,
then there's no reason to be worried.
Right. Um, yeah, exactly. He just said it right there
All right, but we've been thinking about every since that's it and the story if you haven't already worry about
You have no worry about show your ID like I don't get it
Right, but then but then, you know, yeah exactly because you know usually all people only run into trouble
I mean people like if someone has the address
And they really the kid come and you like you know harm to you know your property your side
They can it's like, you know
They're that obsessed and it's like so it's scary that there's people that were to take it outside of the
The internet arena and stuff like that. It's just like you just be very are people like that
There's people who will stalk you and people who will contact your employer and your wife and everybody else
There's plenty of people like that, you know
You to
One hell of a data trial for start plenty of places to go well
You don't have to worry about any that shit because this place isn't full of of
You know those kind of people you know what I mean
People need to be erased so it's good when they
So then you put them behind bars like one less of you on the planet asshole
You know
I'm proud you said a race. You didn't say another word. I was watching the guy's
And someone in the chat swatted him while he was live streaming
No shit. Next thing there's like eight officers show up and they walk and they walk around them and
He says what's this about they say that right now Dougie right now right now?
So it is what you said you want is 150 over here 151 you got the same time
My time 151 yeah
All right, imagine some you can swap right now right now online while you're here imagine that or Alex
I was watching a guy live stream. He got swatted. Well, he was like, I mean filming the offices
Well, he's talking when they talk that doesn't make sense to me though. I wouldn't laugh if that happened
Like hello, why is there a swatting at my house?
Because the mental coldness and said this
I'll be like, uh, look
Hey, it would be funny when they knock down your door when they like, you know
Grant your bedroom when you got up and like maybe push yourself out and then
I would I would love for swath teams to come crumble my house and jump through everywhere and don't try to laugh at them
Like what are you doing here?
like some uh
Or a few colders and said
So now you go get him and put him in jail. Okay, you all fucked up
You're all under now. I'm gonna sue all of you motherfuckers. You understand
What are you doing at my house with armored cars because somebody called
Are you guys that stupid?
Can you verify the cool so anybody that calls anybody and says this is happening in the house
You're gonna run there with all my cars and and kill everybody
That's correct. That's insane. I
would have so hard
Some ways like not to mention one way PD, so I will have human heart
Welcome Kristen Marie welcome
Thank you
Yeah, I love those too, but I he's breathing as you're just yelling so loud
And I want to have like a peaceful pan. I don't want to be screaming about whatever you're screaming about please just like
He's my boy. I love everything else
Well, I
when you come to YouTube voluntarily, no one's forcing anyone to be in YouTube, no one's
got a gun saying, go into YouTube, that you've got to be aware that you take these risks.
Yeah, yeah, I am aware, I'm aware, I don't know what else, your microphone is all the
way up, I'll put it down for you.
I take a risk with Alex because I like it really better Alex no lie way better
People put me through analysis protecting me, okay, who put you through something a ziggie
It doesn't matter dude. Okay. Well remember what you were saying? Remember what you were saying?
Remember what you were saying? Well she was saying last night, she was like, oh
Fuck
Chris, so I love, what are you talking about? Why are you turning on me?
I'm not turning on you. I'm just saying these people
On on your platform that hurt well personal personal I had to like how you know people I had to like you know meet them and
You know kind of like you know
What's it goes dance into the mystery? I know but I had nothing to do with that fight
And you know what it was so funny. It's like two days ago
Uh, you know my fight with beta was last weekend and you guys are talking about it now
But you guys did not like about what she did to
Body you're talking about
And be it be it be it was on the panel with flurry diamonds like for some like you know a couple hours
You know talking about it. So it's like yeah, it was it was covered on the show
I think I think that they came to kind of a
He's all hot. I love
Never I wasn't even there dude. I was not I was
Dude
Are you married? No, are you married?
No, I'm not married
her again and left her and took half of everything you know I'm so on the radar page
she's now lonely and cooking pancakes all alone and uh
huh
Us who's day one? Do they really know who J1 is?
A1 that's my boy in the 1A community. Oh, yep. And no one else will come up here then
And I don't fuck with you
How do you love me, how do you love me hate me so much at the same time? I don't understand
It's like, you know, can't you just have the you know be cordial?
Against you
Oh my god, he just come I didn't call you a faggot. I called that guy a faggot and you're saying
Everything's about me drama drama drama when when when shut up
It's a little crystal crystal crystal crystal. Let's we can work it out crystal
The wrong stories about me, okay, okay
Sometimes I sometimes I you know, right like for comedic effect like elaborate details of story
I like I you know, you know what I say, you know, that's what I do sad you know that you're doing it
Well, it's like, you know, I just, it's just a natural, it's just a natural comic, and so sometimes it's just, you know, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out like, it comes out
That's disrespectful, but no, but it's not disrespectful, but I was definitely disrespectful
Guess why because I really don't doubt and you know my favorite word is faggot
Okay crystal ah
Okay crystal, hold on. Where did you play something crystal?
I don't care about that word. I really don't I'm not offended personally, but I don't want that word set on my show
And so you just had like 10 times when I have to end my stream crystal
Okay, I don't know that you're trying to you can't just like say that word so many times in like a minute
We don't have all these people to turn up like my channel
So thank you crystal and don't say to get up. I'll be back on I'll see you guys this way